rebatesme.com 2018-12-31

# Homepage - RebatesMe - Shopping online and earn cash back

Privacy Policy

We at RebatesMe.com are committed to safeguarding your personal information, and have designed our business practices to safeguard your privacy. This privacy policy applies to your information that we collect and receive; it does not apply to practices of businesses that we do not own or control or to people we do not employ. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you use our services. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices. By using this site, you agree to the terms of this privacy policy.

BROWSING THE SITE

If you browse through the site without entering any personal data, we may gather and store certain information about your visit. This information does not identify you personally and cannot be linked back to you unless you decide at some point to identify yourself. If you are only browsing, we may collect the following information: IP address, the type of browser and operating system used to access our site, the date and time you access our site, the pages you visit (click-through), and if you linked to our website from another website, the address of that website, as well as additional information related to your visit. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to gather geographic related information and to administer the site. 

Third-party advertisements maybe shown on this website. This content is provided through Rakuten Marketing (“provider”) or other provider. Rakuten Marketing is located at 215 Park Avenue, 2nd floor, New York, NY, USA. For more information on the purpose and scope of the data collected and its further processing and use by the provider as well as your related rights and setting options to protect your privacy, please refer our Services Privacy Policy: [https://rakutenmarketing.com/legal-notices/services-privacy-policy](https://rakutenmarketing.com/legal-notices/services-privacy-policy) .  

INFORMATION COLLECTED

There will be times, such as when you communicate with us by e-mail, submit an application for membership, purchase a product, etc., when we will need to obtain personally identifiable information about you. Such personally identifiable information may include your name, home address, e-mail address, telephone number, etc. Consumers who submit an application expressly authorize us to collect information regarding purchases so that their rebates can be recorded. RebatesMe DOES NOT collect any of your credit card information. The information we receive about you may be used by us or shared by us with our corporate affiliates, agents, vendors and other third parties to help process your request or complete a transaction; to comply with any law, regulation, audit or court order; to help improve our website or the products or services we offer; for research; to better understand our customers' needs; to develop new offerings; and to alert you to new products and services in which you may be interested. We may also combine information you provide us with information about you that is available to us internally or from other sources. We believe that knowing more about you can enable us to serve you better. We may also aggregate your personal information with other member's information and prepare reports on site usage, purchase history or other factors for sale or distribution to third parties. However, these reports are aggregated and will not include any personally identifying information. Finally, we may use your personal information to send you email or postal communications regarding products or services offered by us or by third parties with whom we have relationships in which we think you may be interested. We do not share, sell, trade or rent your personal information to third parties for unknown reasons. You may at any time choose not to receive promotional emails from us by contacting us at [service@RebatesMe.com](mailto:service@rebatesme.com). Similarly, if you prefer for us not to provide your name and email or postal address to third parties for direct marketing purposes, please contact us at [service@RebatesMe.com](mailto:service@rebatesme.com). Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may continue to contact you for the purpose of communicating information relating to RebatesMe.com, as well as to facilitate, complete or confirm any transaction that you may enter into or responding to your inquiry or request. We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources:
* \- Information we receive from you on applications on our website or other forms;
* \- Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates, or others;
* \- Information about you we may receive from external data providers.
* \- All information provided by consumers in any of the above-listed ways or otherwise may be used and disclosed as permitted in this Policy. We may also disclose non-public personal information about you to non-affiliated third parties as permitted by law.

COOKIES

We may place "cookies" on your personal computer. "Cookies" are small identifiers, sent from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive, that help us to recognize you if you visit our website again. RebatesMe uses these cookies to determine whether or not you made a purchase at one of our retailer sites. Also, our site uses cookies to track how you found our site. Cookies are not used to get data from your hard drive, your e-mail or any other personal data about you. To protect your privacy we do not use cookies to store or transmit any personal information about you on the Internet. You can reject cookies by changing your browser settings. Please note, however, that if you reject our cookies, RebatesMe cannot track your purchase and you will not earn cash back. It is also possible that some web pages may not properly load, your access to certain information might be denied, or you might have to enter information about yourself more than once.

SECURITY

We safeguard your personal data during electronic transmission from you to us using known encryption, security standards and procedures. We restrict access to non-public personal information about you only to those employees who need to know that information in order to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic and other procedural safeguards to comply with applicable privacy laws to guard your nonpublic personal information. We also assess new technology for protecting sensitive customer information on an ongoing basis. However, if your information is forwarded to a third party provider, your information will be transmitted according to the security and privacy policies of that third party provider whose privacy practices may differ from ours. Your information as shared with outside providers will become subject to those different privacy policies. Due to federal and state regulations, we are required to keep a copy of your information for a period of three (3) years. Over this period, we will maintain all such data in a confidential and secure area that third parties will not be allowed to access.

THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies use non-personally identifiable information regarding your visit to this website and other sites, such as the user IP address, pages viewed, date and time of your visit, and number of times you have viewed an ad, to serve ads to you on this site and other sites that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. In addition, we use clear GIFs or pixel tags to help manage our online advertising. These clear GIFs enable our ad serving company to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits this site. This allows us to learn which banner ads bring users to our website. The information we collect and share through this technology is not personally identifiable.

TRADEMARK AND COPYRIGHT INFORMATION

Everything on our website is copyrighted (unless otherwise noted) and may not be used except with our express written consent. Use of these images by you or other third parties is prohibited and may violate the copyright laws, trademark laws, privacy laws and other laws and regulations. Nothing contained on this site may be construed as granting any license or right to use any of our trademarks or service marks without our prior written consent.

CONTACTING THE WEB SITE

Please be aware that we may change our Privacy Policy from time to time. If we do, we will update this Privacy Policy at our website, so be sure to check back here frequently. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or privacy policies, please feel free to e-mail your questions to us at [service@RebatesMe.com](mailto:service@rebatesme.com) Click to [Log in](https://www.rebatesme.com/login) or [Sign up](https://www.rebatesme.com/reg).
